Africana Center Records UA113
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, circa 1939 -- 2011; UA113.004; 6.64 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects containing 28 files.; 1.086 Megabytes
  - Office files, circa 1983 -- 1993; UA113.004.008.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 52, Box 8)
  - Office files, circa 1983 -- 2000; UA113.004.008.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 53, Box 8)
  - Office files, 1900 -- 1999; UA113.004.008.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 54, Box 8)
  - Office files, circa 1992 -- 1994; UA113.004.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 1, Box 9)
  - Office files, circa 1996 -- 1997; UA113.004.009.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 2, Box 9)
  - Office files, 1998; UA113.004.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 3, Box 9)
  - Office files, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.004.009.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 4, Box 9)
  - Office files, circa 1998 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 5, Box 9)
  - Office files, circa 1999; UA113.004.009.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 6, Box 9)
  - Office files, circa 1999 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00007; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 7-8, Box 9)
  - Office files, 2000; UA113.004.009.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 9-10, Box 9)
  - Office of Student Activities Reference Manual, 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.009.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 11, Box 9)
  - Onyx poetry slam, circa 1990 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 12, Box 9)
  - Onyx records, 1993 -- 1999; UA113.004.009.00011; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 13-14, Box 9)
    Folder 2 of 2 contains 3.5" floppies.
    - Michael Fraser, Onxy – Spring '99, 1999; UA113.004.009.00011.00001
    - ONYX tram shani, 1999; UA113.004.009.00011.00002
  - Orientation and peer advising records, circa 1981 -- 2002; UA113.004.003; 34 Folder(s)
    - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod, circa 1991 -- 1997; UA113.004.009.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 15, Box 9)
    - Cape Cod, 1998; UA113.004.009.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 16, Box 9)
    - Cape Cod orientation and peer advisors, circa 1994 -- 1998; UA113.004.009.00014; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 17-18, Box 9)
    - Cape Cod orientation weekend records, circa 1997 -- 1999; UA113.004.009.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 19, Box 9)
    - Cape Cod orientation weekend and peer advising records, circa 1998 -- 2002; UA113.004.009.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 20, Box 9)
    - Cape Cod sea camps, 2000; UA113.004.009.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 21, Box 9)
    - Freshman, 1997; UA113.004.009.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 22, Box 9)
    - Freshmen orientation, 1993; UA113.004.009.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 23, Box 9)
    - Freshmen orientation at Cape Cod, circa 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.009.00020; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 24-25, Box 9)
    - Freshmen orientation at Cape Cod evaluations, circa 1990 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 26, Box 9)
    - Orientation, 1984; UA113.004.009.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 27, Box 9)
    - Orientation, 1985; UA113.004.009.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 28, Box 9)
    - Orientation, 1986; UA113.004.009.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 29-30, Box 9)
    - Orientation, 1987; UA113.004.009.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 31, Box 9)
    - Orientation and clippings, circa 1981 -- 1983; UA113.004.009.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 32, Box 9)
    - Orientation committee, circa 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.009.00027; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 33-34, Box 9)
    - Orientation committee memo, 1999; UA113.004.009.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 35, Box 9)
    - Orientation response packet mailed to freshmen, 1992 -- 1993; UA113.004.009.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 36, Box 9)
    - Peer advising records, circa 1999 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 37, Box 9)
    - Peer advisors, 1987 -- 1988; UA113.004.009.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 38, Box 9)
    - Peer advisors, 1990; UA113.004.009.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 39, Box 9)
    - Peer advisors, 1991 -- 1992; UA113.004.009.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 40, Box 9)
    - Peer advisor applications, 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.012.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 2, Box 12)
    - Peer advisors list, 1994; UA113.004.009.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 41, Box 9)
    - Peer advisors program, circa 1986 -- 1987; UA113.004.009.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 42-43, Box 9)
    - Peer advisors response forms, 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.009.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 44, Box 9)
    - Peer programing, circa 1994 -- 1995; UA113.004.009.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 45, Box 9)
    - Pre-freshman orientation program, circa 1988; UA113.004.009.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 46, Box 9)
    - Pre-freshman weekend, 1987; UA113.004.009.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 47, Box 9)
    - Pre-orientation letter, 1987; UA113.004.009.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 48, Box 9)
  - Pan-African Alliance event planning, 2002 -- 2004; UA113.004.009.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 49, Box 9)
  - Pan-African Alliance financial records, 1998 -- 2003; UA113.004.009.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 50, Box 9)
  - Pan-African Alliance speaker budgets, circa 1998 -- 2003; UA113.004.009.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 51, Box 9)
  - Parents weekend, 1978 -- 1979; UA113.004.009.00044; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 52, Box 9)
  - Peace Corps, 1993; UA113.004.009.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 53, Box 9)
  - Performances and guest speakers, circa 1980 -- 1986; UA113.004.009.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 54, Box 9)
  - Performing arts: dance, circa 1977 -- 1983; UA113.004.009.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 55, Box 9)
  - Phillips, Denise A. files, circa 1989 -- 2000; UA113.004.009.00048; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 56-58, Box 9)
  - Picnics, circa 1994; UA113.004.010.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 1, Box 10)
  - Postcards, circa 1997; UA113.004.010.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 2, Box 10)
  - Piper, Adrian biography, circa 1998; UA113.004.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 3, Box 10)
  - Prejudice educational options committee, 1987; UA113.004.010.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 4, Box 10)
  - Program Cooperation of America, circa 1976 -- 1982; UA113.004.010.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 5, Box 10)
  - Property office forms, circa 1986 -- 1987; UA113.004.010.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 6, Box 10)
  - Provost dinner RSVP listing 1993-94, circa 1993 -- 1995; UA113.004.010.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 7, Box 10)
  - Publication purchase orders, circa 1969 -- 1986; UA113.004.010.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 8, Box 10)
  - Recruitment records, circa 1969 -- 1991; UA113.004.010.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 9, Box 10)
  - Resident assistant job description, circa 1990 -- 2000; UA113.004.010.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 10, Box 10)
  - Results of communications cluster meeting memo, 1983; UA113.004.010.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 11, Box 10)
  - Riggs, Marlon, 1999 -- 2001; UA113.004.010.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 12, Box 10)
  - Self-assessment: part of the solution is knowing the problem, circa 1975 -- 1985; UA113.004.010.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 13, Box 10)
  - Sexual harassment resource persons meeting, 1997; UA113.004.010.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 14, Box 10)
  - Shady Hill School, 1996 -- 1999; UA113.004.010.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 15, Box 10)
  - Slavin, Jonathan counseling center, 1997; UA113.004.010.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 16, Box 10)
  - Special projects, circa 1978 -- 1981; UA113.004.010.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 17-18, Box 10)
  - Spring planning, circa 1976 -- 1989; UA113.004.011.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 1, Box 11)
  - Standing Room Only award, 2005; UA113.004.011.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 2, Box 11)
  - Total Dance, Dancical Productions, Inc., 1994 -- 1997; UA113.004.011.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 3, Box 11)
  - Tufts University campus directory, 1999; UA113.004.011.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 4, Box 11)
  - Tufts University Employee Handbook, 1996; UA113.004.011.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 5, Box 11)
  - Tufts University Policy on Sexual Harassment, 1999; UA113.004.011.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 6, Box 11)
  - Tufts student resources, 2000; UA113.004.011.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 7, Box 11)
  - Voices from the Heart flier, 1999; UA113.004.011.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 8, Box 11)
  - Writings, circa 1980 -- 1990; UA113.004.011.00009; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_dd5282731d6bec4ee248cd619a6389f4, Folder 9-10, Box 11)
  - 3.5 Floppy disk contents, 1990 -- 2000; UA113.004.012.00003
    - 3.5 Floppy disk contents, 1990-2000; UA113.004.012.00003.00001
    - Africana Center letters of recommendation, 1998; UA113.004.012.00003.00002
      Files are closed for 75 years from date of creation.